

CONTACT

+94 070 5735 453

Maharagama, Colombo, Srilanka

koraad.github.io/myportfolio/

koraad.github.io/myportfolio/

SKILLS

• Web Development

• Shopify and WordPress

• Improvisation

• Creative Design

• Online Marketing

• Content Creation

• Front End Coding

• Problem-Solving & Critical Thinking

Photoshop

• Graphic Design with Canva

• Strong Communication

EDUCATION

BENG (HONS) SOFTWARE ENGINEERING (READING)

University of Westminster, UK 2021 - 2024

HIGH SCHOOL (COMBINED MATHEMATICS)

Wesley College, Colombo 2000 - 2013

CURRICULUM VITAE

DON PASINDU

Web Developer/Online Marketer

OBJECTIVE

Seeking a responsible and challenging position in a growth oriented progressive organization where my Education, Knowledge & Talents will significantly contribute to the overall success of the organization and provide opportunities for my career growth.

PROFILE

I am Don Pasindu Jayith Korottage a creative Web Developer with 3 years of experience in website development, e-commerce and online marketing. Accompanied by strong creative and analytical skills. I am an out of the box thinker, and a team player with an eye for details, who never takes no for an answer.

PORTFOLIO

Checkout my personal portfolio in the following link koraad.github.io/myportfolio/ and https://donpasindujayith.is-great.net/

TOOLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs, VS Code, Github, Shopify, WordPress, Photoshop, Canva, Facebook Ads

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPMENT

Personal Showcase Projects (checkout the portfolio)

2019 - Present

Created some personal projects with HTML,
 CSS and JavaScript which are aligned with
 real world web development projects.

EXTRA CURRICULAR

- Coached the Senior Badminton team of Wesley College, Colombo
 O9 (Assistant Badminton Coach)
- Captained the Badminton team of General Sir John Kotelawala
 Defense University (KDU)
- All Island Junior National
 Badminton Championship in
 2007,2009 and 2010 (Awarded by

 Sri Lanka Badminton Association)
- Captained the Senior Badminton team of Wesley College, Colombo
 09
- Awarded many prizes and certificates at the Annual Inter-House Athletic Meet for 4x100Relay, 4x400Relay, 800 meters, 1500 meters

REFERENCE

MR. MUNESH DAVID

Group Chief Internal Auditor, Dialog Axiata PLC

No.57, Dharmapala Mawatha, Colombo 03, Srilanka.

- +94-077-7088-131
- +94-077-7332-206

Munesh.David@dialog.lk

MR. INDIKA LIYANAHEWAGE

General Manager – Human Resources, Eskimo Fashion No: 44/16. P.O Box 30,

Negombo, Srilanka.

+94-077-3596-616

indika.liyanahewage@gmail.com

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

ONLINE MARKETING

My own e-commerce brands

2020 - Present

- Founded an Activewear e-commerce brand and a Jewelry e-commerce brand and registered my business under the name BODYJENE LLC in USA. (currently not in business)
- Checkout, Bodyjene Activewear Instagram Page https://www.instagram.com/bodyjene/
- Checkout, Stylish Extras Jewelry Instagram Page <u>https://www.instagram.com/stylishextras/</u>

OTHER EXPERIENCE

WNS GLOBAL SERVICES (PVT) LTD, SRILANKA Senior Associate - Quality Operations

Jan 2020-Feb 2020

 Involved in assurance of Quality of subordinates as a Team leader which involved checking the quality of Document Storage Process

HONG KONG & SHANGHAI CORPORATION (HSBC)-HDPL, SRI LANKA

Associate - Financial Crime Risk Operations

Nov 2018-Oct 2019

 Investigated Money Laundering in Department of Financial Crime Risk and Regulatory Compliance as a Financial Crime Compliance Executive.

SRI LANKA ARMY

Officer Cadet

Sep 2015-Nov 2018

 Involved in military exercises, Firing sessions, military tactics and strategies and other administrational work at Sri Lanka Army and followed a Biomedical Engineering Degree Program at General Sir John Kotelawala Defense University (KDU)